 const qstnApi = [
   {
     numb: 1,
     question: "1. What does API stand for?",
     options: [
       "Application Programming Interface",
       "Advanced Programming Interface",
       "All Purpose Interface",
       "Application Process Integration",
     ],
     answer: "Application Programming Interface",
   },
   {
     numb: 2,
     question: "2. How do you make an API request in JavaScript?",
     options: [
       "Using the 'fetch' method",
       "By creating a new 'API' object",
       "Using the 'getAPI' function",
       "None of the above",
     ],
     answer: "Using the 'fetch' method",
   },
   {
     numb: 3,
     question: "3. What is the purpose of the 'localStorage' in JavaScript?",
     options: [
       "To store data on the server",
       "To store data on the client's machine",
       "To interact with external APIs",
       "To create arrays",
     ],
     answer: "To store data on the client's machine",
   },
   {
     numb: 4,
     question: "4. How do you add an item to an array in JavaScript?",
     options: [
       "array.addItem(item)",
       "array.push(item)",
       "array.insert(item)",
       "array.append(item)",
     ],
     answer: "array.push(item)",
   },
   {
     numb: 5,
     question:
       "5. Which method removes the last element from an array in JavaScript?",
     options: [
       "array.removeLast()",
       "array.pop()",
       "array.deleteLast()",
       "array.splice()",
     ],
     answer: "array.pop()",
   },
   {
     numb: 6,
     question: "6. What does JSON stand for?",
     options: [
       "JavaScript Object Notation",
       "JavaScript Output Notation",
       "JavaScript Object Naming",
       "JavaScript Order Notation",
     ],
     answer: "JavaScript Object Notation",
   },
   {
     numb: 7,
     question: "7. How can you convert a JSON string to a JavaScript object?",
     options: [
       "JSON.stringify()",
       "JSON.parse()",
       "convertJSON()",
       "parseJSON()",
     ],
     answer: "JSON.parse()",
   },
   {
     numb: 8,
     question: "8. What is the purpose of the 'localStorage' in JavaScript?",
     options: [
       "To store data on the server",
       "To store data on the client's machine",
       "To interact with external APIs",
       "To create arrays",
     ],
     answer: "To store data on the client's machine",
   },
   {
     numb: 9,
     question: "9. How can you remove an item from an array in JavaScript?",
     options: [
       "array.remove(item)",
       "array.delete(item)",
       "array.splice(item, 1)",
       "array.pop(item)",
     ],
     answer: "array.splice(item, 1)",
   },
   {
     numb: 10,
     question:
       "10. What does the 'fetch' method return when making an API request?",
     options: ["A promise", "An array", "An object", "A string"],
     answer: "A promise",
   },
 ];
